Crime Is King
3000 Miles to Graceland is a action, adventure, comedy
film directed by Demian Lichtenstein.
It was an ingenious enough plan: rob the Riviera Casino's count
room during an Elvis impersonator convention.
But Thomas Murphy decided to keep all the money for himself and shot all
his partners, including recently-freed ex-con Michael Zane.
With $3.2 million at stake, the Marshals Service
closing in, Michael must track down Murphy.
Michael Zane, played by Kurt Russell.
Thomas J. Murphy, played by Kevin Costner.
Cybil Waingrow, played by Courteney Cox.
Hanson, played by Christian Slater.
Damitry, played by Kevin Pollak.
Gus, played by David Arquette.
3000 Miles to Graceland is a 2001 American action crime film
directed and co-produced by Demian Lichtenstein.
The original script was written by Richard Recco and Demian
Lichtenstein shares a co-writing credit on the final film.
The film stars Kurt Russell, Kevin Costner, Courteney Cox, David Arquette,
Bokeem Woodbine, Christian Slater, Kevin Pollak and Daisy McCrackin.
3000 Miles to Graceland was produced by Franchise Pictures and released in the
United States on February 23, 2001, by Morgan Creek Productions, Inc.
(through Warner Bros.
The film received mostly negative critical reviews and was a box-office bomb
making only $18.7 million against its $47.4 million budget.
The film explores themes of prison, robbery, casino, submachine gun, kidnapping.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and intense.